Finding Aid for Sam Sturgis Photograph collection
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Chelsea
  - Lincoln St. residences. Published by LT Freeman and Company., C 1.4 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Middle Street residences as viewed west from East Street in 1914. 1914, C 1.5 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Marl or mare (?) bed at Michigan Portland Cement Co., C 1.6 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Scenic view looking east in 1915 including railroad and Chelsea Elevator Co. 1915, C 1.7 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Glazier Stove Co., C 1.8 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Glazier Stove Co. looking south., C 1.9 --; Copy neg. No print. (Box 5)
  - Main St. looking northwest in 1930. 1930, C 1.10 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Chelsea High School on Harrison St. in 1911. 1911, C 1.11 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - M.E. Home in 1926. 1926, C 1.12 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Summit or Middle (?) Sts. with residences looking east in 1914, C 1.13 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Glazier Stove Co. looking northeast., C 1.14 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Sports Day parade circa 1909, C 1.15 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
    [See also C-3.9 and C-15.1]
  - Sports Day parade circa 1909, C 1.16 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Race track on Sports Day in 1917, C 1.17 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Main St. looking south from South St., C 1.18 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Flanders Manufacturing Company (screw machines)., C 1.19 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Glazier Stove Co. looking south., C 1.20 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Walker Furniture fire at Middle St. on 10 December 1909. 1909, C 1.21 --; Copy neg.. (Box 5)
    [See also C-1.28 and C-8.2]
  - Michigan Central Railroad depot looking south with Penn and Vogel Drugs in background., C 1.22 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Main and South Sts., as seen west from Park St., C 1.23 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Main St. looking north., C 1.24 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Middle St. looking west., C 1.25 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Freeman and Cummings Company exterior with men and boys in front, including Lou Freeman in suspenders. (At Main and Packard Sts.), C 1.26 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Exterior of Chelsea Savings Bank, NW corner Main and South Sts. Built in 1901 by Frank Glazier in memory of his father George P. Glazier., C 1.27 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Walker Furniture Store fire on Middle St. on 10 December 1909. Later site of the Water and Electric Co. 1909, C 1.28 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - New Chelsea High School., C 1.29 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Flanders Manufacturing Co. 9., C 1.30 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
    [See also C-1.31 and C-1.1]
  - Screw Machine Department of Grant and Wood Manufacturing Co., C 1.31 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
    (Photographer: Vogel the Druggist. Source: Wystan Stevens.)
    [See also C-1.19 and C-1.30]
  - Scenic view of Chelsea in 1912. 1912, C 1.32 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - West side of South Main St. in 1907. 1907, C 1.33 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Main St. looking south., C 1.34 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Glazier Stove Co. plant in 1908. 1908, C 2.1 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
    (Source: McKune Library.)
  - Main St. north from South and Park Sts., C 2.2 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Scenic view looking southwest in 1881. 1881, C 2.3 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - First grade at First Elementary School in 1891 located on Park St. between East and Madison Sts. 1891, C 2.4 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Civil War veterans (HP Carpenter, Post No. 41, Grand Republic) at Michigan Central Railroad depot c. 1900. circa 1900, C 2.5 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
    [See also CM-79]
  - Recreation building/assembly hall of Glazier Stove Co., C 2.6 --; Copy neg. No print. (Box 5)
  - Congregational Church in 1902. 1902, C 2.7 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - McKune Hotel/McKune House, now McKune Library. T. McKune, proprietor., C 2.8 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Chelsea School children including two boys from Chelsea's first African-American family in 1889. Teacher, Miss Wheeler. 1889, C 2.9 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - R.S. Armstrong Store exterior on East Middle Street. Left to right: Jim Geddes, Ed Gray, RS Armstrong and either George Foster or David Taylor., C 2.10 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - J.G. Wackenhut family and residence on South Main St., C 2.11 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Exterior Chelsea Bank at Main and Middle Sts. c. 1900, reproduced from a tintype. circa 1900, C 2.12 --; . (Box 5)
    (Published Source: McKune Library. .)
  - Calvin Tompkins of Chelsea Cornet band organized on 19 February 1878. 1878, C 2.13 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - North Main St. looking south toward B & B Stoves office and Glazier Stove Co., C 2.14 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - First automobile in Chelsea., C 2.15 --; Copy neg. No print. (Box 5)
  - Glazier Stove Co. interior., C 2.16 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Group of people on outing in horse and carriage., C 2.17 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Glazier Stove Co. recreation building washroom., C 2.18 --; Copy neg. No print. (Box 5)
  - 1960 census map - Transferred to MHC map collection. circa 1960, C 2.19 --; Copy neg. only. (Box 5)
  - Methodist Church., C 3.1 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Michigan Central Railroad station., C 3.2 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Main Street unpaved and looking north. 1906, C 3.3 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Michigan central Railroad depot on 17 October 1906. 1906, C 3.4 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Methodist Old People's Home., C 3.5 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
    [See also C-21.2]
  - Oak Grove Cemetery., C 3.6 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Red Cross nurses c. 1890 or World War I., C 3.7 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Howlett Home on Chelsea-Dexter Road including woman., C 3.8 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Chelsea Standard float in Sports Day parade -orig. Hoover horse and buggy c. 1910 including Bess Allen and Ethel Burkhardt. 1910, C 3.9 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
    [See also C-15.1 and 1.15]
  - Main Street looking south., C 3.10 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Panoramic view of Chelsea in 1907. 1907, C 3.11 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Congregational Church., C 3.12 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Corner Main and Middle Sts. including businesses., C 3.13 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Exterior Kempf Bank and Webster Tailor in 1918. 1918, C 3.14 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - St. Mary's Church., C 3.15 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Middle Street with residences in 1893. 1893, C 3.16 --; Copy neg.
  - Main Street including Chelsea House in 1893. 1893, C 3.17 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Union School in 1893. 1893, C 3.18 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Middle Street in 1893 with residences Widow's Walk and Belvedere. 1893, C 3.19 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - East Middle Street looking west c. 1900. circa 1900, C 3.20 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Cyclone ruins on 27 June 1914. 1914, C 3.21 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
    (Source: MHC. No print.)
  - Cyclone ruins on 27 June 1914. 1914, C 3.22 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - First Methodist Church in 1890. 1890, C 4.1 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
    (Source: Mrs. Louise Grant.)
  - New Methodist Church on 20 February 1900. 1900, C 4.2 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Homer Ives Home exterior in 1901. 1901, C 4.3 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Post Office site looking north in 1936. 1936, C 5.1 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
    (Source: Richard Schoules.)
  - Post Office site looking east in 1936. 1936, C 5.2 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Michigan Portland Cement Company east of Chelsea in 1911. 1911, C 6.1 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
    (Source: Rose Ann Kalishek.)
  - Panoramic view of entire complex Glazier Stove Company., C 6.2 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Elementary school class at school on Harrison Ave. in 1910. 1910, C 6.3 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Main St. looking north., C 7.1 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
    (Source: Jay Weinberg.)
  - Parade on Middle St. including businesses Glazier Stove Co., Freeman Bros. and S. Holmes Mercantile Co. dept. store., C 7.2 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Grant and Wood Manufacturing Company recreation building., C 8.1 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
    (Source: Joyce Eiseman. Photographer: Vogel the Druggist.)
  - Fire at Walker Furniture Store on Middle St. 10 Dec. 1909, later site of the Water & Electric Co. 1909, C 8.2 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
    (Source: Joyce Eiseman.)
    [See also C-1.28]
  - Chelsea days after Walke Furniture Store fire of 1909. 1909, C 8.3 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Political rally including men, women and children., C 8.4 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Old Michigan Cement Company east of Chelsea in 1911. 1911, C 9.1 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
    (Source: Paul C. Maroney.)
  - Glazier Stove Company and Chelsea Lumber Company before tower and before 1906. 1906, C 9.2 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - East side of Main St. looking south., C 9.3 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Glazier Stove Co., C 9.4 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
    (Source: Paul C. Maroney. Photographer: Fenn and Vogel.)
  - Chelsea High School football team, champs in 1913. Jack Dunn, All-American quarterback holding ball. 1913, C 10.1 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
    (Source: Emmett Hankard.)
  - Morlock's Garage in 1930 on alley off Park St. 1930, C 10.2 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Interior Chelsea Post Office., C 11 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
    (Source: Philip E. Roy.)
  - Seitz Tavern, formerly McNamara's Saloon including (left to right:) George Seitz, George Alber, George Hanner., C 12 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
    (Source: A. Seitz.)
  - Factory equipment at Hollier Automobile Plant., C 13.1 --; Copy neg. No print. (Box 5)
    (Source: Otis M. Titus.)
  - Hollier Automobiles, makers of eight-cylinder passenger autos, manufactured by Lewis Spring and Axle. Advertisement. No print., C 13.2 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Advertisement from Lewis Spring and Axle Co., C 13.3 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Advertisement for B & B Cook Stove Co. in 1895. 1895, C 13.4 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Portrait of CH Kempf, half-tone from newspaper publication., C 13.5 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Kempf Brothers Bank, operated by Charles and Ruben Kempf privately from 1876 to 1899, when incorporated into Kempf Commercial and Savings Bank., C 13.6 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
    (Published. Source: Otis Titus.)
  - Portrait of Frank Glazier and daughter Edna., C 13.7 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Street scenes in Chelsea including Town Hall and looking north, south, east and west., C 13.8 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Front of St. Mary's Sacred Heart Church and cemetery., C 14.1 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
    (Source: Harold Jones.)
  - Rear of St. Mary's Sacred Heart Church and cemetery., C 14.2 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Main St. in front of McKune House with orig. Hoover horse and carriage and passengers Ethel Burkhardt and Bess Allen. (Chelsea Standard, owner of carriage.), C 15.1 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
    (Source: Mrs. LeRoy Hoffman.)
  - Chelsea Tribune Buildings with horse and wagon and women outside., C 15.2 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Chelsea High School., C 15.3 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Glazier State Savings Bank, orig. site of WP Schenk Dry Goods (later razed for bank). Oldest known photo of Main St.?, C 15.4 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Glazier Stove Co. including two girls. (One girl is Edna Glazier.), C 15.5 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Main St. looking north, taken from tintype., C 15.6 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Cyclone ruins on 27 June 1914. 1914, C 16.1 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
    (Published Source: Mrs. H. Lyons. Published by LT Freeman Co.)
  - Washtenaw County's last(?) wolf, killed 8 February 1907. 1907, C 16.2 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
    (Source: Mrs. H. Lyons.)
  - First St. Mary's Catholic School in 1906. 1906, C 16.3 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - First St. Mary's Catholic School after fire in 1925. 1925, C 16.4 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Main St. looking north in 1907. 1907, C 17.1 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
    (Source: John Lotridge.)
  - Tommy McNamara's Saloon, C. Schmidt Shoeshop and Dr. Schmidt, Tom Moore Cigars on Main St. First brick building in Chelsea., C 17.2 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Midnight on west side of Main St. with electricity., C 17.4 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
    (Source: John W. Lotridge.)
  - Chelsea Band in 1909. 1909, C 18 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
    (Source: Mrs. John Hanna.)
  - Interior of Munson Burkhart's Ice Cream Parlor including men, women and patrons., C 19 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
    (Source: Mrs. Glen Wiseman.)
  - Main Street welcome scene., C 20 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
    (Source: Donald Knoll.)
  - Boyd's Hotel on Main St., C 21.1 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
    (Source: Graham Sprague.)
  - Entrance to Methodist Home in 1907. 1907, C 21.2 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - West side of Main St. looking south in 1906. 1906, C 22.1 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
    (Photographer: Fenn and Vogel. Source: Ruby Strieter.)
  - Main St. looking north including Schneider's Grocery Store., C 22.2 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
    (Schneider's was site of Chelsea's first house after it was moved from McKune House location. Source: Ruby Strieter.)
  - North Main St. at Michigan Central RR on 5 July 1906. Wooden ramp led to Wool Co. 1906, C 22.3 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
    (Source: Ruby Strieter.)
  - WP Schenk and Co. on Main St. with men and women in front., C 22.4 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Main St. looking south on 23 April 1906 including HS Holmes Mercantile Co. 1906, C 22.5 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Catholic Church on 1 July 1906. 1906, C 22.6 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Main St. on 27 July 1906 including Glazier Stove Co. 1906, C 22.7 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Catholic School on Congden St. including children. 1906, C 22.8 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Train accident in 1908. 1908, C 22.9 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Veterans group with Chelsea Band., C 23 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
    (Source: Mrs. J. Burg.)
  - St. Mary's or Chelsea's Class C Basketball Champs in 1923. 1923, C 24.1 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
    (Source: Paul Hoffman.)
  - St. Mary's or Chelsea's Class D Basketball Champs in 1926. 1926, C 24.2 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - St. Mary's first and second grades in 1910. 1910, C 24.3 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Exterior Chelsea Screw Plant., C 25.1 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
    (Source: Lilah E. Lantis.)
  - Airplane in hangar in 1922. 1922, C 25.2 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
    [See also CM-12.1, 12.2 and 12.4]
  - Main Street looking north in 1920 with Kalb's Restaurant. 1920, C 25.3 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
    [See also C-25.8]
  - Chelsea Polo Team c. 1920. 1920, C 25.4 --; Copy neg.
  - Girls Dance Group., C 25.5 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Chelsea High School Football Team c. 1928. 1928, C25.6 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Collin's Wolverine Inn., C 25.7 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Main St. looking north in 1926 including Kalb's Restaurant. 1926, C 25.8 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Girls/Womens fashions c. 1920. circa 1920, C 25.9 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - OB McLaughlin's Gas Station in 1929. Gas price 9 7/10 cents per gallon. 1929, C 25.10 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - St. Mary's School Orchestra., C 25.11 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Methodist Home., C 25.12 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Main St. looking south including Chelsea House., C 25.13 --; Copy neg. 5x7 (Box 5)
  - Old residence of Elisa Congdon, first building in Chelsea. Later site of McKune House. Built in 1832., C 26 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
    (Published. Source: Mrs HL Zeeb.)
    [See also CM-20.1 and 20.2]
  - Hiram Pierce House, built in 1831. Oldest known existing house in Sylvan Township on Old US 12 near M 52., C 27 --; Copy neg. No print. (Box 5)
  - Bishop Foley., C 28.1 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
    (Source: Hazel Proctor.)
  - Portrait of baby., C 28.2 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Portrait of children., C 28.3 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Kellogg stop -Mich. Central RR- west of Chelsea in 1908. 1908, C 29 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
- Chelsea-Manchester
  - East Guthrie crossing looking north in 1919. 1919, CM 1.1 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
    (Source: Mrs. Harold Lantis/McManus Negative Collection.)
  - Drainage ditch in 1919. 1919, CM 1.2 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - East Guthrie crossing looking south in 1919. 1919, CM 1.3 --; Copy neg. No print. (Box 5)
  - Farm Light and Power Co. truck in 1919. 1919, CM 2.1 --; Copy neg. No print. (Box 5)
  - Farm Light and Power Co. truck in 1919 including Adam Alber. 1919, CM 2.2 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
    (Source: Mrs. Harold Lantis/McManus Collection.)
  - Beet harvest with three farmers in field., CM 2.3 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Hearse with George Stattan, owner., CM 2.4 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Cemetery in 1914. 1914, CM 3 --; Copy neg. No print. (Box 5)
    (Source: Mrs. Harold Lantis/MNC.)
  - St. Paul's Church in 1918. 1918, CM 4 --; Copy neg. No print. (Box 5)
    (Source: Mrs. Harold Lantis/MMC.)
  - Main St. looking north including automobiles in 1926. 1926, CM 5.1 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
    [See also C-1.3]
  - Main St. looking north in 1926. 1926, CM 5.2 --; Copy neg.. (Box 5)
    [See also C-25.3 and 25.8]
  - South Main St. from road M-17 in 1926. 1926, CM 5.3 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - South Main St. looking south in 1926. 1926, CM 5.4 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Entrance to ME Home in 1926. 1926, CM 5.5 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - ME Home in 1926. 1926, CM 5.6 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Highland costumes in 1918. 1918, CM 6 --; Copy neg. No print. (Box 5)
  - Municipal Building in 1945. 1945, CM 7 --; Copy neg. No print. (Box 5)
  - Grocery store exterior., CM 8.1 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Grocery store., CM 8.2 --; Copy neg. No print. (Box 5)
  - Train accident in 1921. 1921, CM 8.3 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Mailman in front of Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company including horse-drawn carriage and postal truck., Cm 9 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - St. Mary's School girls basketball player c. 1926. Three different shots. 1926, CM 10.1 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Portrait of gentleman., CM 10.2 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Village Orchestra including men and women., CM 10.3 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Girls basketball team., CM 10.4 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Interior of portrait studio (McManus?)., CM 10.5 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Portrait of SR Jackson in 1922, Glazier Stove Co. Executive. 1922, CM 11 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Airplane and three men in 1920. 1920, CM 12.1 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Airplane under construction., CM 12.2 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Building exterior including Fred C. Klingler Meats., CM 12.3 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Three different shots of airplane construction., CM 12.4 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Front of burned building on 17 November 1933 (winter fire 1932?). 1933, CM 13.1 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Rear of burned building on 17 November 1933 (winter fire 1932?)., CM 13.2 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Chelsea Volunteer Fire Department c. 1935, exterior with group. circa 1935, CM 14 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - McLaughlin's Gas Station in 1933 (?). Includes two diff. shots. 1933, CM 15 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Sports Day parade on Main St. c. 1925 including bank, Vogel Pharmacy, Webster Tailor, Steger Dentist. circa 1925, CM 16 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Chelsea Light and Water Department., CM 17 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - 1920 automobile. 1920, CM 18.1 --; Copy neg. No print. (Box 5)
  - 1920 automobile. 1920, CM 18.2 --; Copy neg. No print. (Box 5)
  - 1920 automobile. 1920, CM 18.3 --; Copy neg. No print. (Box 5)
  - Chevrolet dealership in 1927. 1927, CM 19.1 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
    (Source:Mrs. Harold Lantis/MNC.)
  - Chevrolet dealership in 1927. 1927, CM 19.2 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Street scene in 1932. 1932, CM 20 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Street scene in 1932. 1932, CM 20 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Street scene in 1922. 1922, CM 21 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Standard oil station between circa 1924-1926. 1925, CM 22 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Soda parlor in 1927, interior. 1927, CM 23 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Soda parlor in 1927, exterior. 1927, CM 23 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - American oil Co. truck including driver and owner James Park in 1927. 1927, CM 24 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Street scene in 1921. 1921, CM 25 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Group of Chelsea men c. 1923-24. circa 1925, CM 26 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Chelsea parade in 1919. 1919, CM 27 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Staebler Oil Co. in 1924. 1924, CM 28 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Staebler Oil Co. in 1924. 1924, CM 28 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Burg's Drug Store and soda fountain in 1935. 1935, CM 29 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Automobile accident at Interurban station in 1929, Detroit United Lines. 1929, CM 30.1 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Automobile accident at Interurban station in 1929, Detroit United Lines. 1929, CM 30.2 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Cook's Food Products and Sign Painters in 1920. 1920, CM 31 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Overland Garage in 1920. 1920, CM 32 --; Copy neg. No print. (Box 5)
  - St. Mary's School in 1927. 1927, CM 33 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Salem Church in 1937. 1937, CM 34 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Ten-wheel truck in 1932. 1932, CM 35 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Ed Weiss farm in 1928. 1928, CM 36 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Ed Weiss farm in 1928. 1928, CM 36 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - St. John's Church and Parsonage, Rogers Cor(?)., CM 37 --; Copy neg. No print. (Box 5)
  - Construction in 1933. 1933, CM 38 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Church interior in 1933 including group and clergyman. 1933, CM 39 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - School in 1933. 1933, CM 40 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - St. Mary's Church in 1934. 1934, CM 41 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Glick's Department Store in 1942. 1942, CM 42 --; Copy neg. No print. (Box 5)
  - Princess Theater on Main St. in 1914. (Two different views.) 1914, CM 43 --; Copy neg. No print. (Box 5)
  - Kitchenware Show inside auditorium, view of stage in 1935. 1935, CM 44.1 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Kitchenware Show inside auditorium, view of all-female audience in 1935. 1935, CM 44.2 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Residence with group outside in 1929. 1929, CM 45 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Dancer home and family. Two different shots., CM 46 --; Copy neg. No print. (Box 5)
  - Cemetery on Hall Road in 1918. Four different shots. 1918, CM 47 --; Copy neg. No print. (Box 5)
  - Main St. drug store interior in 1949, including H. Fenn and two clerks. Two different shots. 1946, CM 48 --; Copy neg. No print. (Box 5)
  - Congregational Church in 1949. 1949, CM 49 --; Copy neg. No print. (Box 5)
  - Resting farmer in 1918. 1918, CM 50 --; Copy neg. No print. (Box 5)
  - Federal Screw Works in 1941. 1941, CM 51 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Federal Screw Works in 1930, former site of Glazier Stove Co. Two diff. shots. 1930, CM 52 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Hoover Steel Ball Co. in 1930. 1930, CM 53 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Six-wheel truck in 1930. 1930, CM 54 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Copy of Chelsea area map in 1927. 1927, CM 55 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Congregational Church in 1945. 1945, CM 56 --; Copy neg. No print. (Box 5)
  - Sewage plant in 1945. 1945, CM 57 --; Copy neg. No print. (Box 5)
  - St. Paul's Church in 1920. 1920, CM 58 --; Copy neg. No print. (Box 5)
  - Concrete mixer in 1918. 1918, CM 59 --; Copy neg. No print. (Box 5)
  - Parade in 1919. Two diff. shots. 1919, CM 60 --; Copy neg. No print. (Box 5)
  - Parade in 1919. Two diff. shots. 1919, CM 61 --; Copy neg. No print. (Box 5)
  - Parade in 1919. 1919, CM 62 --; Copy neg. No print. (Box 5)
  - Landscape/scenic view in 1918. 1918, CM 63 --; Copy neg. No print. (Box 5)
  - Birth and marriage records in 1927. Four diff. shots. 1927, CM 64 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Glazier Stove Co., six diff. shots in 1922. 1922, CM 65 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Broom display stand in 1921. Two diff. shots. 1921, CM 66 --; Copy neg. No print. (Box 5)
  - Four diff. portraits of Mr. Herman and Mrs. Davis Dancer., CM 67 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Two children and dog in front of Bonnie Brae Country Club in 1927. 1927, CM 68 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Vermont Cemetery Marker in 1925. 1925, CM 69 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
    (Marker cites names of early Chelsea settlers from Vermont including Davis, Fenn, Lawrence, Warner, Wines and Spaulding. Published. Source: Mrs. Harold Lantis/MNC.)
  - Chelsea Screw Co., CM 70 --; Copy neg. No print. (Box 5)
  - Front of Chelsea Standard in 1944. 1944, CM 71 --; Copy neg. No print. (Box 5)